<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="no_help_available">
      There is no help available at this time.
    </string>
    <string name="about_help_topics">
      Help is available for each section of this app.
    </string>

    <string name="help_page_intro">For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below.</string>
    <string name="help_page_intro_html">
    <![CDATA[
      For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below:
       ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section1">Recording</string>
    <string name="help_text_section1">
     How to record a trip
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section1">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        You can turn on the recording either in the map view (first icon with the paw) or else in the summary view (by tapping the paw icon).
        This will start to record a location at the invterval you defined in the settings. Note that if you don\'t have the GSP turned on, 
        it will use the much less accurate network locations. 
        </p>
      <p>When you exit the application, if you like you can tell the app to keep recording locations. That way,
      you can use your device in other ways while still tracking your location.
       </p>
      <p>
      The locations are stored in a local db and are uploaded to a server of your choice if you like.
       </p>
       
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
      ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section2">Uploading</string>
    <string name="help_text_section2">
         <![CDATA[
     How to upload the data to a server
       ]]>
    
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section2">
    <![CDATA[
       <p>
     If you like you can upload the locations to a server. Where and how to do it is completely up to you - we provide free sample
     code on our sever on how to do it. By default it will be uploaded to our server.
     On the server it is stored in a database, and you can look at it with any application, such as with php, Java or Vaadin.
     </p>
     To turn on uploading, tap the last icon on the map view (the icon with the signal tower), or tap the same icon in the summar view.
     In settings you can decide how often and to where you wish to upload your locations. 
     <p>
     We provide free source code on how to do this with php, Vaadin (Web based Java framework) or with a Java servlet, 
     with code on how to use it with google maps.
     </p>
      <p>
        <a href="http://www.myegotrip.net">Egotrip web page</a>.
      </p>
     
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>


    <string name="help_title_section3">Managing trips</string>
    <string name="help_text_section3">
      What you can do with a trip
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section3">
    <![CDATA[
      <p> 
     A trip is composed of locations, and each location can have an icon, an image and a text attached to it.
     </p>    
      <p>
     To attach information to a location, open the Map and click on the edit icon (the second icon with the pen).
     Then, tap any location and you will get a context sensitive menu. 
     The menu also has options to move or delete a location and to split a trip.
     If you ever wish to merge a trip, all you need to do is rename the current trip to the trip you wish to merge into ;-)
      </p>
   
      <p>
      <b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section4">Your server</string>
    <string name="help_text_section4">
          <![CDATA[
     How to set up a server
     
       ]]>
    
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section4">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
     What you need to do to set up your own server
      </p>
      <p> 
        <a href="http://www.myegotrip.net">Egotrip web page</a>.
        </p>
     
      <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
